Herz, John H.; Papers ger015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- General correspondence, 1938-2005; 2; 124 file folders
  - Iring Fetcher, 1966; 1974 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Ossip K. & Lili Flechtheim, 1944; 1958-1998 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Hans D. Fleischauer, 1984-1985 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Abraham Flexner, 1940 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Bernard Flexner, 1939 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 33)
  - William T. R. Fox, Undated (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Daniel Frei, 1974-1976; 1985 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 34)
  - John H. E. Fried, 1985 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Toni Friedlaender, 1964 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 34)
  - J. W. Fulbright, 1966 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 34)
  - G - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 35)
  - J. W. Garner, 1938 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Jürgen Gasper, 1992-1993 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Felix Gilbert, 1948; 1969; 1976; 1988; 1989 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Horst von Gizycki, 1981; 1985 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Peter Goddard, 2005 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Dietrich Goldschmidt, 1980; 1995-1996 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 37)
  - M. Greiffenhagen, 1964 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Fritz Grüters, 1929-1948 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Gisela Grüters, 1973-2003 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Hilde Grüters, 1974-2001 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Otto Grüters, 1967 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 39)
  - H - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Christian Hacke, 1978-1990 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Christian Hacke, 1991-1998 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Christian Hacke, 1999-2005 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Edvard Hambro, 1951 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Sungjoo Han, 1973-1974 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 44)
  - M. Donald Hancock, 1978 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Wolfram F. Hanreider, 1969-1971 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 44)
  - David Harris, 1963 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Wilfried Heidt, 1975 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Samuel Hendel, 1976 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Gregory Henderson, 1973-1983 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Alan K. Henrikson, 1976 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Anni Herz, 1974 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Gerhard Herz, 1969-1985 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Herbert Herz, 1964-1974 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Steven Herz, 1982-2002 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Werner Herz, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Helmut Hirsch, 1965-1997 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Stanley Hoffmann, 1962; 1999 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Margaret Hofmann, 1969 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Hajo Holborn, 1960 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 49)
  - H. Stuart Hughes, 1951 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Julian Huxley, 1950 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 49)
  - I, J - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Hans - Adolf Jacobson, 1980-1983 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Egbert Jahn, 1990 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Oscar Jászi, 1939 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Martin Jay, 1970 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Inge Jens, 1990-1995 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Jim Jensen, 1974 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Robert Jervis, 1978-1980 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Philip Jessup, 1939-1940 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Hans & Ilsedore Jonas, 1986; 1991; 1999 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Susanne Jonas, 1999 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Steven Jonas, 1988 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Irmgard Jordan, 1974-1977 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 55)
  - K - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 56)
  - Ludwig Kahn, 1992 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Richard Kaplan, 1985 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 57)
  - K. William (Ted) Kapp, 1970 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Thomas G. Karis, 1984; 1999-2005 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Doris Karmin, 1984; 1988; 1990 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 59)
  - Margaret P. Karns, 1984-1985 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 59)
  - Barry M. Katz, 1984-1986 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 60)
  - Hans Kelsen, 1951; 1964; 1966; 1971 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 61)
  - George Kennan, 1980; 2004 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Stephen D. Kertesz, 1961 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Mario Kessler, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Otto Kimminich, 1975-1977 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 62)
  - Gottfried - Karl Kindermann, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 62)
  - Jupp & Lore Kingsley, 1975 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 63)
  - Fred Klestadt, 1968; 1979-1984 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 63)
  - Wilfrid Kohl, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 63)
  - Donald P. Kommers, 1971 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 63)
  - Choong-Suk Kong, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 64)
  - Karlheinz Koppe, 1980-1982 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 64)
  - Pekka Korhonen, 1983 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 65)
  - Erica Korody, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 65)
  - Melvin Kranzberg, 1978-1980 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 65)
  - Albert Kraus, 1984 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 65)
  - Joseph Kruzel / James Rosenau, 1984-1988 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 66)
  - Erich Küchenhoff, 1968 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 67)
  - H. J. (Gong Xiangrui) Kung, 1983 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 67)
  - Josef L. Kunz, 1938 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 67)
  - L - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 68)
  - J. J. Lador-Lederer, 1975-1976 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 69)
  - Martin Landau, 1970 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 69)
  - Stein Ugelvik Larsen, 1985 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 69)
  - Thomas B. Larsen, 1962 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 69)
  - Joel Larus, 1963 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 69)
  - Jong Chan Lee, 1987 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 69)
  - Gerhard Leibholz, 1963-1976 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 70)
  - Thedor Leuenberger, 1974-1975 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 70)
  - Ernst Levy, 1938-1939 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 71)
  - Mordechai & Nada Levy, 1963-1986 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 71)
  - Guenter & Ilse Lewy, 1962; 2001 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 72)
  - Werner Link, 1975-1983 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 72)
  - Grete Lippmann, 1984 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 72)
  - Karl Loewenstein, 1940-1972 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 73)
  - Richard Loewenstein, 1970 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 73)
  - Nita M. Lowey, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 73)
  - M - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 74)
  - Andreas Maislinger, 1986-1987 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 75)
  - Erika Mann, 1964 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 75)
  - Vojtech Mastny, 1975-1982 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 75)
  - Frederick H. Mayer, 1977 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 76)
  - Hans Mayer, 1982-1985 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 76)
  - Erich Mayer-Schneider, 1952; 1984-1990 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 77)
  - Charles A. McClelland, 1959 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 78)
  - George McKenna, 2004 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 78)
  - Frank Mecklenburg, 1985-1993 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 78)
  - Monika Medick-Krakau, 1982-2001 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 79)
  - Manuel Medina, 1972-1974 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 79)
  - Aladár Métall, 1938-1939 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 80)
  - Hans Meyerhof, 1951 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 80)
  - Friedrich Middelhauve, 1958 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 80)
  - Stefanie Middendorf, 2002 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 80)
  - J. V. Minghi, 1968 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 81)
  - Ben Mollov, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 81)
  - Hans Morgenthau, 1943; 1949-1950; 1979-1980 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 81)
  - Steven Muller, 1962 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 82)
  - Melvin Mutzner, 1984 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 82)
  - Andreas Mytze, 1988 (Box 3 (2-General correspondence), Folder 82)
  - N, O - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Franz Neumann, 1951 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Walter Neumann, 1974-1975 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Reinhold Niebuhr, 1952 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Gottfried Niedhart, 1986 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Lutz Niethammer, 1973; 1979; 1982 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Peter von Oertzen, 1974-1975 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 3)
  - P, Q - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Henry M. Pachter, Undated (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Jay Kyu Park, 1974-1989 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Albert Phiebig, 1995; 1997 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Uwe Prell, 1986-1996 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Uwe Prell, 1997-2005 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Jana Puglierin, 2005 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 8)
  - R - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Ellen Rafshoon, 1994-1996 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Inge & Mitja Rapoport, 1982; 1990-1996; 2001 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Johannes Rau, 1974-1975 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Ogden R. Reid, 1971 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Benjamin Rivlin, 1986-1988 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Romano Romani, 1970 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Richard N. Rosencrance, 1962-1964 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - James N. Rosenau, 1968-1971 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Joel H. Rosenthal, 1992 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Dankwart A. Rustow, 1985-1987 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - S - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Christoph Sachsse, 1985 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Abdul A. Said, 1966-1968 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Albert Salomon, Undated (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Will Schaber, 1984; 1994-1995 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Maria Schlegtendal, 1970-1976; 1984; 1992 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Monika S. Schmid, 1998-1999 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 16)
  - George Schwab, 1974-1978; 1991 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Andrew M. Scott, 1968 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Paul Seabury, 1959-1963 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Peter Seidel (re: Invisible Walls), 1987-2002 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Rudolf Serkin, 1984 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Robert Sharlett, 1978 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Hans Simons, 1938-1939 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Richard Sklar, 1984 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Ansgar Skriver, 1984-1986 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Jerome Slater, 1986-1987 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Louis L. Snyder, 1965-1977 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 21)
  - R. Soekardjo, 1960 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 21)
  - John M. Spalek, 1979; 1980; 1982; 2002 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 21)
  - James P. Speer, 1967; 1985-1986 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Kurt Steiner, 1986 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Richard Sterling, 1971 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Frank Stern, 1988-1993 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Fritz Stern, 1966-1974 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Roberto Sternau, 1985 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Dolf Sternberger, 1978 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Peter Stirk, 1999 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 24)
  - John G. Stoessinger, 1968 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Matthias Stoffregen, 1996-2002 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Gerald Stourzh, 1968; 1978; 1987 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Eckhard Stuff, 1982-1986 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Richard N. Swift, 1962-1980 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Istvan Szent-Miklos, 1972 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 26)
  - T, U - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Klaus Täubert, 1998 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Marion (Flechtheim) Thimm, 2005 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Kenneth Thompson, 1951-1952; 1979-1980; 1993-2001 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Piet Tommisson, 1992 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Clifford Truesdell, 1937-1945; 1989-1990 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 30)
  - G. L. Ulmen, 1984; 1992; 2002 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 30)
  - V, W - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Detlev Vagts, 1989-1990 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 32)
  - John A. Vieg, 1951 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Stanley Volansky, 1977 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Gert Von Eynern, 1974-1975 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Vope, Renate, 1999 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Nicholas Wahl, 1960 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Walter, Conston, Alexander & Green, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Kenneth N. Waltz, 1967; 1969 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Henry Wasser, 1984 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Hermann Weber, 1985 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Hans Wehberg, 1951; 1959 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 34)
  - John Wellemeyer, 1963 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Erich Wenderoth, 1960-1993 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Wilhelm Wengler, 1949-1951 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Martin Wight, 1961-1962 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Richard Winston, 1966 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Frederick M. Wirt, 1962-1964 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Klemens Wittebur, 1983 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Arnold Wolfers, 1962 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Steve Worth, 1970 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Gong Xiangrui, 1982 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Gordon C. Zahn, 1961 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Luyping Zhang, 1981-1985 (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous unidentified correspondence, Undated (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Recommendations, A - F, Undated (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Recommendations, G - L, Undated (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Recommendations, M - Z, Undated (Box 4 (2-General correspondence), Folder 42)
- Correspondence with publishers, co-editors, contributors to volumes, 1949-1995; 3; 84 folders
  The first section of this series is arranged chronologically according to the date of the specific publication and contains extensive correspondence with co-editors Gwendolen Carter and Louise Holborn and Otto and Anne Kirchheimer, correspondence with publishers, royalty statements, as well as correspondence with contributors to essay volumes. The second section of the series is arranged alphabetically by the name of the publishing house or periodical publication.
  - Political Realism and Political Idealism (1951) - University of Chicago Press, 1950-1985 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 43)
  - Political Realism and Political Idealism - Anton Hain Verlag, 1954-1959 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 44)
  - Political Realism and Political Idealism - Woodrow Wilson Foundation Award 1951, general correspondence, Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 45)
  - Major Foreign Powers (1952-1975) - Harcourt, Brace & Co., 1950-1962 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 46)
  - Major Foreign Powers - Harcourt, Brace & Co., 1963-1985 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 47)
  - Major Foreign Powers - Royalty statements, 1952-1975 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 48)
  - Major Foreign Powers - Gwendolen Carter, 1950-1964 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 49)
  - Major Foreign Powers - Gwendolen Carter, 1965-1986 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 50)
  - Major Foreign Powers - Earl Latham, Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 51)
  - Major Foreign Powers - Carl E. Schorske, Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 52)
  - International Politics in the Atomic Age (1959) - Columbia University Press, 1957-1985 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 53)
  - International Politics in the Atomic Age - Royalty statements, 1960-2003 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 54)
  - Government and Politics in the Twentieth Century (1961-1973) - Frederick A. Praeger Publishers, 1963-1986 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 55)
  - Government and Politics in the Twentieth Century - Royalty statements, 1961-1975 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 56)
  - Documents of Major Foreign Powers (1968) - Louise W. Holborn, 1956-1975 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 57)
  - Otto Kirchheimer memorial volume (1969) - notes by Herz, miscellaneous correspondence, Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 58)
  - Hermann Luchterhand Verlag, 1966-1967 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 59)
  - Frederic S. Burin, 1965-1968; 1990 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 60)
  - Val R. Corwin, 1966 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 60)
  - Arkadij Gurland, Undated (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 60)
  - Arnold J. Heidenheimer, 1966; 1970 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 60)
  - Erich Hula, 1966-1969 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 61)
  - Otto Kirchheimer, 1952 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 62)
  - Anne Kirchheimer, 1965-1985 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 62)
  - Wolfgang Luthardt, 1975-1979; 1984-1989 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 63)
  - Kurt L. Shell, 1965-1968 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 64)
  - German Constitutional Documents Since 1871 - Frederick A. Praeger Publishers, contract, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 1)
  - Divided Nations - general, 1974 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 2)
  - Staatenwelt und Weltpolitik (1974) - general correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 3)
  - Staatenwelt und Weltpolitik - Hoffmann und Campe, 1973-1976; 1992 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 4)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy (1983) - notes, copyright information, general correspondence, 1978-1983 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 5)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Greenwood Press, 1982-1984 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 6)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Giuseppe DiPalma, 1979-1982 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 7)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Frederick Engelmann, 1979-1982 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 8)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Michael Fichter, 1979-1982 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 9)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Klaus-Dietmar Henke, 1979-1981 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 10)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Hans Adolf Jacobsen, 1979 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 11)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Béla Király, 1982 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 12)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Manfred Knapp, 1979-1980 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 13)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Jutta-B. Lange Quassowski, 1980-1984 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 14)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Juan Linz, 1979-1983 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 15)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Roy Macridis, 1980-1982 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 16)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Edward Malefakis, 1979-1982 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 17)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Kenneth Maxwell, 1979-1983 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 18)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Karlheinz Niclauss, 1979-1982 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 19)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Lutz Niethammer, 1979-1980 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 20)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Harry Psomiades, 1981-1982 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 21)
  - From Dictatorship to Democracy - Arthur Tiedemann, 1979-1982 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 22)
  - Vom Überleben (1984) - general correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 23)
  - Vom Überleben - Berg Publishers, Limited, 1983-1986 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 24)
  - Vom Überleben - Campus-Verlag, 1983-1984 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 25)
  - Vom Überleben - Droste Verlag, 1959; 1984-1995 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 26)
  - Vom Überleben - Duke University Press, 1987-1991 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 27)
  - Vom Überleben - Landeshauptstadt Düsseldorf, 1983-1984 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 28)
  - Vom Überleben - Suhrkamp Verlag, 1983-1984 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence with publishers, ), Folder 29)